K.
Okay. Now you start the recording. And now if there's no motions or anything else you wanna do, you make a motion to adjourn and that's it.
Who wants to make the motion to adjourn?
How are you feeling to you? Are you better or?
I have
terrible headache. It's killing me. I made the motion to adjourn the meeting.
Nothing. I can touch it. I've taken every pill I can think of. Nothing was touching it. Yikes.
I hope you feel better soon. I I I feel your pain. I'm so sorry. I got a sick kid at home right now who's taking all sorts of
random symptoms. So bizarre.
Second,
the motion ujer.
We have a first.
I did.
All
in favor.
Aye.
Alright. Thank you guys. You for all your input. Thank you for all the work, Diane. Yeah. Thank you.